{
  "title": "Japanese Greetings and Phrases Quiz",
  "description": "Test your knowledge of essential Japanese greetings and phrases with this quiz. From 'Good morning' to 'Thank you' and beyond, each question provides options, a hint, and the correct answer in Japanese characters and Romaji. Immerse yourself in the politeness and cultural nuances of Japanese expressions!",
  
    "items": [
      {
        "question": "おはようございます",
        "answer": "ohayou gozaimasu",
        "options": ["ohayou gozaimasu", "konnichiwa", "konbanwa", "arigatou"],
        "hint": "The Japanese greeting for 'Good morning.'"
      },
      {
        "question": "こんにちは",
        "answer": "konnichiwa",
        "options": ["ohayou gozaimasu", "konnichiwa", "konbanwa", "arigatou"],
        "hint": "The Japanese greeting for 'Hello' or 'Good afternoon.'"
      },
      {
        "question": "こんばんは",
        "answer": "konbanwa",
        "options": ["ohayou gozaimasu", "konnichiwa", "konbanwa", "arigatou"],
        "hint": "The Japanese greeting for 'Good evening.'"
      },
      {
        "question": "ありがとう",
        "answer": "arigatou",
        "options": ["ohayou gozaimasu", "konnichiwa", "konbanwa", "arigatou"],
        "hint": "The Japanese expression for 'Thank you.'"
      },
      {
        "question": "ごめんなさい",
        "answer": "gomen nasai",
        "options": ["gomen nasai", "itadakimasu", "oyasuminasai", "arigatou"],
        "hint": "The Japanese apology phrase for 'I'm sorry.'"
      },
      {
        "question": "おはしをください",
        "answer": "ohashi o kudasai",
        "options": ["ohashi o kudasai", "itadakimasu", "oyasuminasai", "arigatou"],
        "hint": "The Japanese phrase for 'Please give me chopsticks.'"
      },
      {
        "question": "いただきます",
        "answer": "itadakimasu",
        "options": ["gomen nasai", "itadakimasu", "oyasuminasai", "arigatou"],
        "hint": "The Japanese expression said before eating, similar to saying 'Bon appétit.'"
      },
      {
        "question": "おつかれさまでした",
        "answer": "otsukaresama deshita",
        "options": ["otsukaresama deshita", "itadakimasu", "oyasuminasai", "arigatou"],
        "hint": "The Japanese phrase used to thank someone for their hard work, similar to saying 'Thank you for your hard work.'"
      },
      {
        "question": "おやすみなさい",
        "answer": "oyasuminasai",
        "options": ["oyasuminasai", "itadakimasu", "ohayou gozaimasu", "arigatou"],
        "hint": "The Japanese phrase for 'Good night.'"
      },
      {
        "question": "わたしは にほんご がくせい です",
        "answer": "watashi wa nihongo gakusei desu",
        "options": ["watashi wa nihongo gakusei desu", "itadakimasu", "oyasuminasai", "arigatou"],
        "hint": "The Japanese phrase for 'I am a Japanese language student.'"
      }
    ]
  }
  